<title>Slug Slasher</title>
<author>Slapped Silly Studios</author>
<date>Summer 2018</date>

<@body>
#(/wc/img/SlugSlasher_Header.png)[left]
((_*Slug Slasher* is a 2D action platformer where the player takes on the role of a chef who must defend the world from an onslaught of giant slugs with only his trusty bucket of salt. Fight your way through crumbling cityscapes, the depths of the slug caverns, or even the glittering gastropod gladiator arenas of Slug Vegas—all the while smashing, dashing, and slashing your way through ridiculous enemies and crazy bosses!_))

((Slug Slasher was originally pitched in Gamedev@IU's predecessor, Hoosier Games, by Ryan Reske during the spring semester of 2017. In addition to Ryan's work as a designer and producer, Dakota Erickson has served as lead systems and level designer, and Rajin Shankar has produced all of the game's code and art.))

#(/wc/img/SlugSlasher_MGC.png)[right]
((Since that first semester, the three-person team has continued development alongside their roles as officers of Hoosier Games. With showcases at various Indiana University events, Indy Pop Con 2017 and 2018, and the Midwest Gaming Classic, the game has received great feedback from sidescroller veterans and casual players alike.))

((The game is poised to launch on [https://store.steampowered.com/app/823590/Slug_Slasher/][PC, Mac, and Linux] during the summer of 2018, with a potential Nintendo Switch release later in the year.))

#(/wc/img/SlugSlasher_Boss.png)[left]
((_"With vibrant visuals, satisfying and punchy sound design, and classic side-scrolling platformer beat-em-up gameplay, Slug Slasher is sure to charm even the saltiest of souls both young and old—so salt up your boots and get slashin' in this slime-packed adventure!"_))

((Check the game out at [http://slugslasher.com/][slugslasher.com] and be sure to follow [https://twitter.com/SlugSlasher][@SlugSlasher] on Twitter for more updates!))
</@body>

<&thumb>/wc/img/SlugSlasher_Header.png</&thumb>
<~hidethumb>true</~hidethumb>